<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_memoirs_1_of_2_name">
		<text>A stalker's journal (part 1 of 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_memoirs_1_of_2_desc">
		<text>An old, faded notebook slipped into a card sleeve in order to protect it from wear and tear. However, it didn't withstand the passage of time well and only a small part of the text is legible:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"I have to write this down, somehow I feel it will lessen my burden, and I can only hope that someone will read it so that my legacy remains after I'm gone and no one makes the same mistakes I did. I don't have a lot of friends, and I most certainly don't have any friends here in the Zone. The traders all look at me like I'm some kind of an outcast. That bearded fellow in Zaton smiles sarcastically every time he sees me, and the Hawaiian trader mocks me with his easy-going attitude. Fuck those bastards, all I need from them is some ammo, food and water from time to time.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]I started writing this so at least someone would know what I went through that night, what happened, and maybe understand why I prefer to be alone at all times. I came here on my own, but immediately paired up with this newbie. It turned out he was a mineral enthusiast. He had a hobby of collecting rocks, and had so many different ones, so naturally the artefacts - strange rocks, unique to the Zone - were his next step up. He got so many of them I can only assume that it was thanks to them that he got this fat tumor in his stomach. Frequent throwing up, diarrhea, stress and the like, you know. He was like a pregnant woman, but instead of a baby he had this malignant, gigantic tumor. He even named it after his first pet puppy. I didn't object, he was good company, and I needed that at the time. We never attacked bandits, avoided most mutants, and just hung around anomalies, picking interesting rocks and sometimes grabbing a few artefacts if we were lucky."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_memoirs_2_of_2_name">
		<text>A stalker's journal (part 2 of 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_memoirs_2_of_2_desc">
		<text>An old, faded notebook slipped into a card sleeve in order to protect it from wear and tear. However, it didn't withstand the passage of time well and only a small part of the text is legible:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"There was talk about this anomaly, reportedly located deep inside a cave or fissure in the ground. There were supposed to be crazy amounts of artefacts, but for some reason nobody wanted to go there. "Cowards and fools," we thought. Why the hell wouldn't anyone jump at the chance to get rich, and live an easy life ever after? So we felt this sudden surge of courage, packed up, and went directly to the cave. We didn't even manage to peer into the cave, and this dark shadow flew over us. I tripped, struck my head when I feel, and just blacked out. After a while I came to, and heard something or someone moaning. "Animals,” I thought at first, but then I realized that it was my friend lying in front of me. I saw his skin ripped all over his body, saw his muscles bleeding all over and saw the bones sticking from disgusting wounds. He was clumsily holding his now exposed guts with his hand, while he was crawling further out of the cave. It was miracle he didn't die on the spot. "What the hell happened?," I couldn't make sense of anything. I still had my backup pistol, and by a defense mechanism of some sort I started shooting towards the darkness of the cave. I had 20 rounds in that pistol, and switched to single fire. When I still had 7 rounds, something grabbed my hand, and made me pull the trigger. At that time I didn't even realize where my gun was pointed and where I was shooting but I couldn't stop. And suddenly the force let go of me, but I was in such a shock that I kept pulling the trigger a few minutes after the magazine was already empty. I knew if I had stopped, I'd have had to face what I did to my friend. I didn't even have the courage to take his dog tags. I just ran. How could I talk to someone or have another friend, when the Zone could take them too? It's better to be alone. Friendship comes with a price and a risk. The short-lived warmth of friendship is not worth it, if you could lose that friendship in the worst imaginable way. I have this bump on my head now to remind me of that. "\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_freedom_manual_1_of_2_name">
		<text>Interrogation techniques: the basics (part 1 of 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_freedom_manual_1_of_2_desc">
		<text>An instructional leaflet with a large Freedom emblem at the upper right corner and a simple drawing of a hand-gun pointing at a kneeling human figure. It is titled "Interrogation techniques: The basics" and is written in a typical, laid-back slang of the faction:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"I shouldn't even tell this 'cause it's so obvious, but really, don't spread the word, don't show this manual around, don't sell it. Throw it away, burn it or only give it to those that you trust most. You don't want everyone knowing this. What if they use it against you? Do you have a stash? So do yourself a favor and keep this to yourself. Don't say I didn't warn you.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Everyone has a stash. Even the poorest, most miserable bandit that has ever lived in the Zone has a couple of food rations and some ammo rounds. It's just the way things work here. You gather some money, sell a few artefacts or mutant parts, loot some dead but usually still warm bodies, and you buy food or weapons so when the shit hits the fan you don't have to stare directly at the fan with a stupid grin on your face but instead have some stuff up your sleeve that can save your sorry ass. These are harsh times and this is a harsh place, and when you fail here, nobody's gonna help."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_freedom_manual_2_of_2_name">
		<text>Interrogation techniques: the basics (part 2 of 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_freedom_manual_2_of_2_desc">
		<text>An instructional leaflet with a large Freedom emblem at the upper right corner and a simple drawing of a hand-gun pointing at a kneeling human figure. It is titled "Interrogation techniques: The basics" and is written in a typical, laid-back slang of the faction:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"But guess what, you can take advantage of that better-safe-than-sorry attitude. If you wanna get a nice, juicy info about the whereabouts of someone's stash, remember to choose your victim carefully. When that's done and when all preparations are complete - you know, the place, there's no one around and the sort, just fuck with them psychologically. Shoot them in the legs or arms, drain their willpower, make them feel pain until they see you as their closest friend in the whole world. And one moment they will just throw their weapons and kneel before you. Talk to them, be nice but firm, helpful but persuasive. Don't kill them, they are human beings after all and the mutants are so numerous, so let's not make the Zone worse than it already is. Besides, you still want the stash, don't you? Tell them you'll cut their face off, scare the shit out of them, make them think it's actually the end so that they won't even need the stash after you're done with them. They usually give it up immediately and run away."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_letter_1_of_2_name">
		<text>Memoir (part 1 of 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_letter_1_of_2_desc">
		<text>A couple of pages torn off from a memoir. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. Author unknown.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"I can still feel the heat of that anomaly on my back. It burns even when I'm sitting in Skadovsk, in a safe place, far from danger and as far from any of those fucking furnaces as it gets. So really, you can only imagine what I have to go through when I do get near an anomaly. Ah, hell, it burns even more of course. It's my organic anomaly detector now, for God’s sake. When you get hit by a burner anomaly or poisoned by a toxic one, that shit doesn't come off easily or even at all. It's like you've taken a part of the Zone inside you, for life. "Marked by the Zone," I guess. But the nightmares... They are the worst. When you experience those abominations of physical laws, you lose every drop of confidence you've ever had. Imagine that: I can handle ten bloodsuckers that appear in front of me in the dead of night. This stuff is easy, I'm a hardened warrior, you see. But the fact these anomalies violate every single law of science is just frightening. Is it even possible? Is what I know to be real real at all? I can't stop thinking that the Zone itself is a bad dream and I want to wake up so much that I wake up into another nightmare, right into the Zone again. That repeats a few times until my heart starts pounding and I jump out of the bed screaming and all sweaty. You'll go deep down the rabbit hole if you follow this logic."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_letter_2_of_2_name">
		<text>Memoir (part 2 of 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_letter_2_of_2_desc">
		<text>A couple of pages torn off from a memoir. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. Author unknown.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"Every time I think about it, my back shivers in pain and turns into this red mess. I haven't even been close to an anomaly for the last 4 months, trying to make my living through hunting, but you know that its never an option in the long run for those like us. That fucking thing still reacts as if it had a mind of its own. Sometimes I wish I hadn't escaped from that burning farmstead. Maybe I'd have been of more use to everyone if I had become food for those boars. Probably not... But the boars, they are stupid fuckers too, running into burners by the dozens. If that farmstead didn't exist, Skadovsk would be overrun by boars in a matter of days. No amount of ammo could keep them at bay, if it wasn't for the Burnt Farmstead, this barbecue factory. And the boars are so freaking useless, the meat's horrible, so charred that no cook can make it even remotely edible. Sometimes I go to Zaton to watch the fireworks, even though the skin on my back hurts so much I can barely hold my backpack. I come back 'cause I feel that I've left something there, something that calls onto me from time to time. Because of that wretched scar on my back and the feeling of burning, I have to sleep on my stomach or sides. I hate sleeping on my sides, I've always been a back sleeper. The Zone forces changes on you and doesn't ask for permission."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_report_1_of_3_name">
		<text>Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 (part 1 of 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_report_1_of_3_desc">
		<text>A machine-typed document stamped with the Ecologist research team emblem. Classified as strictly confidential and signed by:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Arkady Cvetkovsky\n%c[0,170,170,170]Junior Science Officer of Laboratory and Research Bunker RX12\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 \n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Date: 19.03.2014\n%c[0,170,170,170]Packet: 34\n%c[0,170,170,170]Page: 1 of 3\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]These "zombies", which is the term locals use when referring to the specimens, are barely a living being, let alone sentient. Scientific data indicates that their brains do not conduct any thought processes and their neurological activity is virtually nonexistent, thus making them fundamentally brain-dead. However, field trials have proven that - for reasons as of yet unknown to science - they are capable of simple mechanical reactions (reminiscent of instinct, but their logic substantially differs). One theory states that this is the result of a never ending neurochemical barrage that compels the body to move in a specific manner in response to certain stimuli. When threatened, they demonstrate extremely violent behavior, so it is advisable to approach them with great care and caution. As far as their physiology is concerned, out test have revealed a peculiar - and potentially scientifically fruitful - ability to self-sustain body parts, which means that such parts are able to function even when separated from the main body and without access to any nutrients whatsoever. One of the most successful endeavors of the scientific team entailed sustaining a liver and a heart for over 3 months despite them being not connected to other organs and bloodstream. Further analysis does not suggest any molecular or subatomic peculiarities.\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] scientific item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_report_2_of_3_name">
		<text>Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 (part 2 of 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_report_2_of_3_desc">
		<text>A machine-typed document stamped with the Ecologist research team emblem. Classified as strictly confidential and signed by:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Arkady Cvetkovsky\n%c[0,170,170,170]Junior Science Officer of Laboratory and Research Bunker RX12\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Date: 19.03.2014\n%c[0,170,170,170]Packet: 34\n%c[0,170,170,170]Page: 2 of 3\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Our findings could provide the basis for a valid explanation as to why, after being shot numerous times in their limbs or pelvis, in their peripheral organs and other areas, they are capable of functioning almost indefinitely without severe difficulties. Walking is usually impeded, running is completely out of the question, but the reflex of aiming with weapons and pulling the trigger seems unaffected. This also applies to the use of other tools and some of the less complicated devices.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Please abstain from using the terms "kill" or "destroy" when referring to the deactivation of a specimen. This stems from the psychological argument that the term "deactivation" is more neutral than "destruction", and can serve as a way of distancing ourselves from the seemingly human form they manage to maintain and of suppressing the feeling of remorse after "deactivating" a specimen. Deactivation requires physically severing the link to their motor system. This would entail inflicting damage to the brain or spinal area, preferably by means of ballistic trauma. Every member of the scientific team should bear in mind that their limbs will remain mobile even after deactivation, therefore special precautions are advised. Especially effective is the physical removal of cervical vertebrae or brain stem with surgical instruments or, in case of their unavailability, any sharp object.\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] scientific item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_report_3_of_3_name">
		<text>Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 (part 3 of 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_report_3_of_3_desc">
		<text>A machine-typed document stamped with the Ecologist research team emblem. Classified as strictly confidential and signed by:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Arkady Cvetkovsky\n%c[0,170,170,170]Junior Science Officer of Laboratory and Research Bunker RX12\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Date: 19.03.2014\n%c[0,170,170,170]Packet: 34\n%c[0,170,170,170]Page: 3 of 3\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]In extremely rare cases certain "zombies" exhibit behaviour reminiscent of more sophisticated animals: they drop their weapons or refuse to engage in a fight altogether. These specimens are of great value to our research, hence deactivation is not advised. Isolation and further analysis in laboratories is of utmost importance. Neuropsychologists are an especially interested party due to the potential for brain stem transplants that could theoretically aid patients in late stages of Alzheimer's and other diseases.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Whenever possible, avoid damaging kidneys and heart upon deactivation as these organs possess immense potential provided transplants ever prove viable. Harvesting organs from immobile "zombies" is also a possibility, however it is recommended to be cautious of local stalkers who might have emotional ties to some specimens. If an encounter with a stalker is unavoidable while harvesting, there are two courses of action one can take in order to minimize the chance of combat. First, when dealing with inexperienced stalkers showing them the eyes of a given specimen has proven very effective, especially since the pupils are completely unresponsive and the eyeballs as such appear inhuman. Secondly, more seasoned stalkers are usually easier to be reasoned with as they can suppress emotions better. However, it is still advisable to make us of psychological expertise when dealing with local human population as in some cases rational communication is completely out of the question.\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] scientific item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_prayer_1_of_3_name">
		<text>Monolith prayer (part 1 of 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_prayer_1_of_3_desc">
		<text>An untitled document comprising a few paragraphs one below another. Frequent references to the Monolith indicate a religious nature of the written text. The paper is preserved very well, which suggests that it has been treated with great care and respect so that its condition doesn't deteriorate. The text of the prayer reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]We are praying to You!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Our only Light in the darkness\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]With hope in our hearts we march!\n%c[0,170,170,170]We march forward towards the infidels!\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Forgive our sins!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Show us our Destiny!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Give us Power to fulfill our purpose!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Give us Hope to slay Your enemies!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Share your Light with us!\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]We pray to you!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]We are your progeny!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Our only hope at redemption!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Your name is in our hearts!"\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_prayer_2_of_3_name">
		<text>Monolith prayer (part 2 of 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_prayer_2_of_3_desc">
		<text>An untitled document comprising a few paragraphs one below another. Frequent references to the Monolith indicate a religious nature of the written text. The paper is preserved very well, which suggests that it has been treated with great care and respect so that its condition doesn't deteriorate. The text of the prayer reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"Warriors of Monolith, we stand!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith, our Light!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Take our souls, our minds\n%c[0,170,170,170]And cleanse them!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Rid them of doubts and hesitation!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith, our Hope!\n%c[0,170,170,170]We are Your soldiers!\n%c[0,170,170,170]We want to give our lives for You\n%c[0,170,170,170]We want to give our souls for You\n%c[0,170,170,170]And we want to be one with You!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith, we shall remove all obstacles from Your path!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Take our flesh!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Take our blood!\n%c[0,170,170,170]Take our souls!\n%c[0,170,170,170]And make them whole again!\n%c[0,170,170,170]You are in us, oh Monolith."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_prayer_3_of_3_name">
		<text>Monolith prayer (part 3 of 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_prayer_3_of_3_desc">
		<text>An untitled document comprising a few paragraphs one below another. Frequent references to the Monolith indicate a religious nature of the written text. The paper is preserved very well, which suggests that it has been treated with great care and respect so that its condition doesn't deteriorate. The text of the prayer reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Oh Monolith!\n%c[0,170,170,170]You are our destiny.\n%c[0,140,140,140]And we are brothers.\n%c[0,140,140,140]We are brothers of the Monolith's Light.\n%c[0,140,140,140]We shall die for Your cause.\n%c[0,140,140,140]We shall die in Your name.\n%c[0,140,140,140]We shall die for Your Light.\n%c[0,140,140,140]Death is only the beginning.\n%c[0,140,140,140]We march with Your name on our lips, oh Monolith!"\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolithian_thoughts_name">
		<text>Monolithian's journal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolithian_thoughts_desc">
		<text>A hand-written sheet of paper. At the beginning, the writing of the note is extremely chaotic and untidy as if the person writing it was suffering from a severe mental disorder. Interestingly, the further down the sheet, the text becomes more plain, letters much clearer and the last words are written with an almost perfect, machine-like precision. The text of the note reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"As far as I can remember, there was darkness around me, and I couldn't see anything. Nothing... For hours. But suddenly I saw a light! A light so bright, a light so cozy... I wanted to touch it, I wanted to feel it. I knew that it was trying to help me, to save me. I knew...\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]And after I touched that light, I forgot everything. There was no life behind me - there was only darkness behind me. The only light was in front of me. Its name is Monolith. It saved me, and I'm eternally grateful. Sometimes I can see the faces, faces from the past... A woman and a child... My family? I'm dressed in white overalls... Maybe I was a scientist... This weird word... Radar... NO! This is that darkness! It wants me to die! I WON'T LET IT KILL ME! There is no way back! There is only light in front of me! Towards the light! For the Monolith!"\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_to_outside_name">
		<text>A letter to Natalie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_to_outside_desc">
		<text>A letter apparently written by one of the stalkers to someone outside the Zone, most probably his wife or lover. The fact that you hold it in your hands suggests that it never reached the intended recipient.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"Hello, Natalie!\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]How are you? How are the kids? Tell Sanya that if he won't listen to you, I will smack him good when I return home. What about me? Well, I don't think that you'll understand. The Zone... This place is... Unique. Only here can I really feel the bonds with other people. Only here can I see them for who they truly are. There are no masks here, only truth. But, like I said, I'll tell you more next time we meet. I've earned some good money here! We can finally buy you that necklace you wanted so much. Oh, and thank you for your letters. They really lift my spirits. When I think about you, everything seems a lot better. We will meet each other soon. Say hello to the kids for me!\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Lots of love. Your Michail. Your brave Stalker."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_military_stalker_name">
		<text>Military stalker's note</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_military_stalker_desc">
		<text>A note found in a stash. It is difficult to determine why it was written in the first place. Most probably, someone was killing time during a long and boring night and then decided to leave the result of his work behind rather than throw it into the campfire. The text of the note reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"Oh yeah. I'm a Military Stalker. This is something unbelievable. Best equipment. Best objectives. Best weapons. Best everything! Finally we've called a truce between the military and the Stalkers. We don't have to shoot each other for once. And this is great - we all are Slavs so we should stick together. What about marauders? Fuck those motherfuckers! It's always great to put a bullet right between their eyes. I'm just a noob here, in this squad, but I already feel that I've become a real man - strong and important. And that's good."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_mercenary_name">
		<text>Mercenary's note</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_mercenary_desc">
		<text>A note written by one of the Mercenaries. Looks like he decided to write down some thoughts concerning his activities in the Zone. The purpose of it is unclear.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"So, from what I can see, there is nothing special here. We are still mercenaries, we are still soldiers of fortune. However, we can choose what we do and what we don't. Sometimes we don't even apply for a certain job because it is too "dirty" for us. If the client wants to kill some good folks earning a living by sweat and toil - fuck this bastard. They always can go to the Zone and deal with their problems themselves. What about marauders, deserters and other scumbags - always yours. Any time, any place. When we have to PROTECT ourselves - it's another matter. But if you want to kill an innocent man - ask those American dolls. They're not so choosy as who to kill. We're different. Bear this in mind next time you give us your money."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_military_log_name">
		<text>Communication log / MSRC operation / 05.04.2014 18:36:21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_military_log_desc">
		<text>A printed transcription of the radio transmission between military units stationed in the Zone. The fact that it was in possession of one of the SKAT unit members indicates that he must have been involved in a clandestine operation, most probably concerned with the extraction of surveillance data. The transcription reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"- HQ, this is MSRC 1-03. We've got photos of NII. 240 photos of an anomaly in the Swamps, about 1400 photos of the main base. When do we return?\n%c[0,170,170,170]- MSRC 1-03, this is HQ. Do not come back for now. There are some problems at the Military Warehouses. MSRC 4-07 is asking for help. Again. This time, however, their SOS signal is strong so we at least know that they are alive.\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Eh, roger that, HQ. Chopper?\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Negative. There are too many anomaly fields in NII Agroprom now, it's too dangerous. Go to Yantar, our MI-24 will pick you up there.\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Roger. Any information about the next blowout?\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Positive. Sacharov said that there are two days left at least. But hurry anyway. Their information has never been reliable.\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Understood. We are on our way, tell the Bird to be at Yantar in 7 hours. MSRC 1-03 out.\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Wait, 1-03. What about the underground in N-2? Did you find anything there?\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Positive. We have found that new anomaly. It looks like some sort of teleport. This should be interesting for those bigheads from Yantar, our detectors fried when we tried to measure psi-fields. Dunno why, possibly because of electronic waves.\n%c[0,170,170,170]- Roger that, MSRC 1-03. Good luck on your way to Yantar. Hear from you in 7 hours. HQ out."\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_stalker_letter_3_name">
		<text>Letter to Nikolai</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_letter_stalker_letter_3_desc">
		<text>A hand-written letter addressed to Nikolai. Most probably a part of a longer written conversation between two stalkers. Although correspondence in the Zone is conducted mainly by means of PDA messages, some prefer a traditional manner of communication, especially in case of most private matters and between friends. These letters are then handed to couriers who, like guides, are entrusted with some of the most difficult and dangerous tasks. It often takes a few days before a letter reaches its recipient, but still the probability of intercepting the message is much lower than in case of PDA communication. The courier profession is highly regarded among fellow stalkers and entails a position of significant influence in the stalker community. The letter reads:\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]"Nikolai,\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]I've just gotten back from my trip to the center of the Zone. It was hell. The Monolith and the army are still going at it, bent on exterminating each other for no reason. One moment it looked like they would conclude a cease-fire, but eventually nothing came of it. Constant havoc and destruction followed and I didn't have any other choice but to escape from this place. I almost got killed once, freaking psycho bastards -but I don't  blame them, entirely my fault, I just wasn't paying attention when it mattered most. This way or another, after some hardships, I made my way to Pripyat and I plan to lie low here for a while. Getting back to what we discussed previously, it seems like we're gonna have to put off our mission until it gets safer out there. I didn't get a moment of sleep after I got back, but I wanted to let you know I'm good, at least physically. We'll stay in touch.\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Take good care, Rua"\n \n%c[0,140,140,140]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] personal belongings\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[0,140,140,140] usable for:%c[0,170,170,170] weapon maintenance (+1%)</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
