<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options">
		<text>Features (Options)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_aoe_pickup_mode">
		<text>AoE pickup mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_aoe_pickup_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Area-of-effect pickup mode%c[default] enables picking up of multiple items at once.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWhen enabled, this feature allows you to pick up multiple items and put them in your inventory with a single key-press, just as you could in Call of Pripyat.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_artefact_degradation">
		<text>Artefact degradation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_artefact_degradation_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Artefact degradation%c[default] causes artefact abilities and bonuses to degrade when activated.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this feature enabled having the best artefacts is no-longer the end of the line for artefact hunters.\n
			\nArtefacts will become weaker the more they are used, promoting their further hunting and accumulation, instead of becoming just a quick source of income.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_azazel_mode">
		<text>Azazel mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_azazel_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Azazel mode%c[default] allows you to continue playing as another character after death.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nIn Azazel mode death is not the end - upon the demise of your character you will posses the body of a random stalker who was previously controlled by the AI.\n
			\nShould you have companions at the time of your death, they will be given priority and you will continue playing as one of them instead.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_delayed_repairs">
		<text>Delayed repairs</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_delayed_repairs_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Delayed repairs%c[default] allows technicians to retain your equipment.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this feature enabled, broken weapons, outfits, and other items which you bring to a technician will be kept in their possession until they have completed all repairs.\n
			\nAfter handing over your items you can speak with the technician again to ask whether they are ready for pick-up, to which they will either return them or tell you how much time they still require.\n
			\nThis adds a somewhat realistic enhancement to the traditional repair system, suitable if you are seeking a harder experience, as it will no-longer work instantaneously and instead emphasise the use of gunsmith and sewing kits.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_dynamic_news">
		<text>Dynamic news</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_dynamic_news_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Dynamic news%c[default] allows stalkers to report on their experiences in the Zone.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nStalkers will comment on events that they have seen or heard near their location, or on their current activities, using the PDA communications network.\n
			\nThese events and activities can range from something as mundane as complaining about the price of goods sold by a trader, to requesting help from faction allies when under attack.\n
			\nMany other features also tie into the system; stalkers may comment on suspicious activity when you are hunting a bounty, giving you an idea where your target is, or may mention if somebody has a job available.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_extended_hud">
		<text>Extended HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_extended_hud_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Extended HUD%c[default] allows the display of additional on-screen information.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this feature enabled brief companion information and a miniaturised version of the artefact belt are made visible on the heads-up display.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the UI/HUD options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_hardcore_ai_aim">
		<text>Hardcore AI aim</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_hardcore_ai_aim_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Hardcore AI%c[default] aim increases AI aim predictability and decreases reaction times.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this feature enabled it becomes harder for you to avoid being hit whilst strafing and sprinting, with the use of cover becoming much more essential to your long-term survival.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_helicopter_patrols">
		<text>Helicopter patrols</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_helicopter_patrols_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Helicopter patrols%c[default] enables factions the use of air support to defend strategic areas.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nFactions who have friendly aircraft patrolling in the area will be able to call on them for support in attacking, or defending from, enemy stalkers (including you) and mutants.\n
			\nDespite their intimidating appearance they can be easily taken down after receiving a light amount of damage to the tail rotor.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Locations%c[default]\n
			\n• Agroprom\n• Cordon\n• Darkscape\n• Great Swamp\n• Limansk
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_ironman_mode">
		<text>Ironman mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_ironman_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Ironman mode%c[default] adds an indirect layer of difficulty to gameplay, whereby all of your saved games for a character are deleted upon their death.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nShould Azazel mode be enabled at the same time you will be allowed to continue playing as whoever you switched to, but saves made as your deceased character will be deleted as per usual.\n
			\nNote that all saves in an ironman mode playthrough are tagged with a unique identifier so the game can distinguish between them, making it impossible for unrelated saves to be deleted by mistake.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_online_exclusion">
		<text>Online exclusion</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_online_exclusion_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Online exclusion%c[default] creates a no-spawn zone around your character.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nAs you explore near the edges of levels and their entry/exit points you could be attacked by enemies arriving from other levels. With online exclusion enabled these spawns are delayed until you are safely out of the way.\n
			\nIt should be noted that this system revolves entirely around you; any enemies already at a location whilst you are changing levels will not be de-spawned upon your arrival.\n
			\nThis feature can be adjusted from the game options menu and is set to 25 by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_population_factors">
		<text>Population factors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_population_factors_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Population factors%c[default] modify the number of stalkers and mutants found in the Zone.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nStalker and mutant population factors can be adjusted independently from one another, allowing you to decide how wild or settled the Zone should be without the need to modify any of the game's files.\n
			\nIt should be noted that the effect is greatest when starting a new character, as if the factors are changed during a playthrough in progress, they will only be realised as stalkers and/or mutants die and then respawn in greater or smaller numbers.\n
			\nThese features can be adjusted from the game options menu and are set to 0.5 by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_portrait_by_outfit">
		<text>Portrait by outfit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_portrait_by_outfit_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Portrait by outfit%c[default] changes your portrait based on your current outfit.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this feature enabled, every time you equip or unequip an outfit (not including headgear) your character's portrait will be updated to reflect this, mimicking how portraits for the AI match with how they look.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the UI/HUD options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_radio_music">
		<text>Radio music</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_radio_music_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Radio music%c[default] allows for custom music tracks to be played at certain locations.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nCertain relaxed areas within the Zone have radios installed nearby, with each playing a selection of musical tracks to keep stalkers entertained.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Locations%c[default]\n
			\n• Agroprom - Military base\n• Cordon - Sidorovich's bunker\n• Great Swamp - Clear Sky base\n• Dark Valley - Bandit base\n• Rostok - 100 Rads\n• Red Forest - Forester's tower
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_sleep_deprivation">
		<text>Sleep deprivation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_sleep_deprivation_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Sleep deprivation%c[default] allows time and the use of consumables to fatigue your character.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nThroughout the Zone you will find many beds and sleeping bags, normally they are only used to allow the you to skip time by sleeping, however with this feature enabled they become an essential part of gameplay.\n
			\nAs time passes your character will slowly begin to feel tired, with the screen beginning to blur and shake. These effects will proceed to get worse until you find a suitable place to rest or the effects of sleep deprivation cause you to collapse from exhaustion.\n
			\nTiredness can be accelerated through consuming items such as medical kits and vodka, and negated with those such as high-caffeine energy drinks - however using too many will leave you unable to rest until their effects wear off.\n
			\nThis feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_story_mode">
		<text>Story mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_story_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Story mode%c[default] enables a non-linear story based on the events of Shadow of Chernobyl.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this mode enabled you start the game with the 'Mysteries of the Zone' storyline, and the tasks of disabling both the Brain Scorcher and the Miracle Machine.\n
			\nTo begin the story you will need to find an important individual hiding somewhere within the Zone, who after a brief dialogue will provide you with multiple tasks which can be completed in any order.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Availability%c[default]\n
			\n• Clear Sky\n• Duty\n• Ecologist\n• Freedom\n• Loner\n• Mercenary\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_survival_mode">
		<text>Survival mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_options_survival_mode_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Survival mode%c[default] turns the Zone into a hunting ground - where you are the prey.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nWith this mode enabled all spawns are replaced with zombified stalkers and mutants, who will slowly stumble towards your location in an attempt to kill you.\n
			\nExclusive to this gameplay mode are zombies themselves, the last devolution of zombified stalkers who have lost the ability to operate mechanical devices such as firearms.\n
			\nOnly a few traders and stalker squads can be found, meaning you will have to survive off of what you can scavenge in the world.\n
			\nThis mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>